<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
	<text>
		<body>
			<pb facs="iiif21481manifest#f000" n="1" xml:id="F705623"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705623">
				<fw type="pageNum">1</fw>
				<dateline>Name &amp; <lb/> Ranke<lb/> Sr. Ldr. <name>Ann Smith</name></dateline>
				<p xml:id="OTP705623P1">Organization<lb/> WAAC Detachment</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705623P2">Branch of service A.A.B<lb/> Hunter Field, Savannah, Georgia</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705623P3">POSTMARK<lb/> SAVANNA GA<lb/> MAY 12<lb/> 11:30 AM<lb/> 1943</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705623P4"><name>Mrs. G.W. Carlstead</name><lb/> 1102 Dillon Drive<lb/> St. Louis, Mo</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705623P5">220 Hengu{?} Dr<lb/> Ferguson, Mo<lb/></p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="iiif21481manifest#f001" n="2" xml:id="F705624"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705624">
				<fw type="pageNum">2</fw>
				<opener>
					<dateline>Hunter's Field<lb/> Savannah, Georgia.<lb/> <date>May 10, 1943</date>.</dateline>
				</opener>
				<salute>Dear Kids: -</salute>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P2">I received your card today and thanks a lot . We arrived here Saturday morning<lb/> and believe me it is so hot we are about to die, we thought it was hot in <name>Fort Oglethorpe</name> but nothing like this.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P3">We are having an awful time here with the girls, there are just twenty one<lb/> girls here at the present time and about eight thousand men and some of the<lb/> girls are sure crazy.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P4">I relly do not know any thing to write that you would be interested in for <lb/> I am so busy trying to get all of the supplies in and getting every thing<lb/> ready for the other one hundred and fifty girls that are expected at any<lb/> time now.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P5">Is <name>George</name> going to <name>California</name> or has he given up the idea?</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P6">I really have to nice here, I have a nice big desk all of my own and a <lb/> typewriter that no one else is allowed to use without my permission and I <lb/> think I will need a lot of practice. I have a jeep and ride around in with<lb/> a chauffer to drive it. I have to go all over the post getting stuff.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705624P7">It is time for the big shot to come in and sign some papers so I can go<lb/> so I guess I had better ring off for this time.</p>
				<closer>
					<signed>Write often Love<lb/> Mother</signed>
				</closer>
			</div>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>