<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
	<text>
		<body>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705562/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="1" xml:id="F705562"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705562">
				<fw type="pageNum">1</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705562P0">that was taken the first day we were here. We had on enlisted men's coats on the way to the warehouse for uniforms. Please send full instructions as to how to use your camera. We don't seem to be able to get it focused right. So I haven't used the second roll of films. Well this week tells the story whether I get to come home and what I will be doing. We are all getting curious. I am still holding out for Motor Corps.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705562P1">I talked to <persName type="name">Peggy</persName> and <persName type="name">Mildred </persName>the other night. I guess you have seen them and they told you if anything serious should happen at home and you would want me call <placeName type="place">Red Cross Headquarters </placeName>there and tell them the situation and request emergency furlough. Also have the Dr. call them.</p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705563/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="2" xml:id="F705563"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705563">
				<fw type="pageNum">2</fw>
				<opener>
					<dateline>Women's Army Auxiliary Corps<lb/> For <placeName type="place">Des Moines, Iowa</placeName></dateline>
				</opener>
				<p xml:id="OTP705563P1">For <placeName type="place">Des Moines, IA</placeName><lb/> Monday Noon</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705563P2">Dear Kids,</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705563P3">Received box yesterday and did I ever appreciate it. Those dates were really good. I was on special detail yesterday. Officers mess. They are trying to convert me into being a cook and I won't be converted for that is not what I want. It is a shame the way they waste food. Gallons of coffee, great chunks of butter and every thing else throwed out. For dinner yesterday: carrot sticks, soup, stuffed celery, roast duck and dressing, potatoes, asparagus, aspic salad, hot rolls and butter, coffee, milk, fresh strawberry shortcacke with ice cream.</p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705564/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="3" xml:id="F705564"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705564">
				<fw type="pageNum">3</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705564P0">a college graduate.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705564P1">Tues noon. Just finished eadting dinner.<lb/> 2pm. Just set down and was called out on the double to report to supply room for scarf. Now I am in class and just heard that we would be free from next Wed until Mon. So I would like to come home so if you want me send me some money this weekend so I can ask for my pass as soon as possible. I understand your own basic training will be finished then and we will know what corps we will be in and what we are going to do. I feel like a school kid going to school so much.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705564P2">I have started and stopped so much since I started to write this letter. I don't know what I am doing. You have never sent me <persName type="name">Al</persName>'s address.</p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705565/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="4" xml:id="F705565"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705565">
				<fw type="pageNum">4</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705565P0">Supper - Every kind of cold meat: ham, beef, pork, salami, etc; cheese; sliced tomatoes; olives; celery; carrot sticks; potato salad; cottage cheese; all kinds of cookies and ice cream.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705565P1">Tues morn. Another line or two. The whole Co. had a party int he day room last night. They are picking 10 from each platoon and then they will be eliminated down to 10 from the Co for OCS this week. I can't make it for you have to have a high school education. I understand it is the first time that they have taken girls right from basic.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705565P2">How are the boys and <persName type="name">G.W.</persName>? Take good care of them.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705565P3">Is it very cold there? Seems as</p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705566/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="5" xml:id="F705566"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705566">
				<fw type="pageNum">5</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705566P0">Has he been down lately? What did he have to say? <persName type="name">Peggy</persName> has never wrote to me and <persName type="name">Mildred</persName> owes me a letter.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705566P1">Well guess I had better ring off for this time. Write often.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705566P2">Love,<lb/> <persName type="name">Mother</persName></p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705566P3">The fare will be $8.50 and I won't get Pullman's for we can't get rates if we do. It doesn't hurt me to set up and sleep.</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705566P4">M.</p>
				<signed/>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705567/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="6" xml:id="F705567"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705567">
				<fw type="pageNum">6</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705567P0">3</p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705567P1">Women's Army Auxiliary Corps<lb/> For <placeName type="place">Des Moines, Iowa</placeName></p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705567P2">tho it can't get above zero. It <lb/> was 23 below zero yesterday a.m.<lb/> Are you working? If you see <persName type="name">Norma</persName>, <lb/> tell her I am still waiting for an<lb/> answer to my card. Had a nice<lb/> letter from <persName type="name">Jill</persName>. Also one from <lb/><persName type="name"> Mrs. [Stella?]</persName>. She said she was <lb/> going to send me some candy.<lb/> <persName type="name">Emma Smith </persName>treated me to a<lb/> supper in <placeName type="place">Des Moines</placeName> Sat. night. <lb/> She must have plenty of money. $1.85<lb/> a [piece?] for a steak. She was the<lb/> one that had the twin sister that<lb/> took the examination &amp; then backed<lb/> out. Her sister &amp; sweetheart are coming <lb/> up Sat.<lb/> My girl friend from <placeName type="place">Miss.</placeName> got <lb/> sent to Bakers &amp; Cooks Sat. She is<lb/></p>
			</div>
			<pb facs="https://fromthepage.com/image-service/705568/full/full/0/native.jpg" n="7" xml:id="F705568"/>
			<div xml:id="OTP705568">
				<fw type="pageNum">7</fw>
				<p xml:id="OTP705568P0">Aux. <persName>Ann Smith</persName><lb/> Co. 2. Reg. 3<lb/> First WAAC Training Center<lb/> Fort <placeName type="place">Des Moines. Iowa</placeName></p>
				<p xml:id="OTP705568P1"><persName type="name">Mrs. G. W. Carlstead</persName><lb/> 1102 Dillon Dr.<lb/> <placeName type="place">St. Louis</placeName><lb/> <placeName type="place">Mo.</placeName></p>
			</div>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>